

# Angelina Rabiieva

08/25/1999

rabievochka2508@gmail.com | Wroclaw, Poland

# QA Engineer

#### SUMMARY.

I'm QA Engineer experienced in mobile/ web/ API/ DB testing.

I would like to continue improving my professional qualifications. I always try to use recent developments.

I'm an energetic and imaginative person who is able to work alongside other talented IT professionals in creating websites and applications meeting the highest standards. I'm an ambitious person who would like to be noticed, full of energy that is really needed to introduce some variety in a project.

#### **TECH SKILLS**

## QA

Web testing;

Knowledge of software testing theory;

Analysis of documentation;

Writing test cases, checklists and bug reports;

Knowledge of Agile methodologies;

Basic knowledge (HTTP, html, TCP / IP, API); P

ractical skills of using Jira, Testrail, Chrome devtools;

Understanding the client / server architecture;

Scrum teamwork with meetings (daily and retro).

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **QA Engineer NOLIMIT SCHOOL**

NOLIMIT SCHOOL • 01/2023 - 04/2023

**Company Description** 

Manual testing of web project;

Estimate, prioritize, plan testing activities; Writing bug reports JIRA issue tracker);

Taking part in the meetings (daily, retro, demo); Working culture of a scrum team

Analysis of technical documentation; Creating test cases;

Performing thorough regression testing;

Analyzing documentation;

### An administrator in a restaurant

#### Oskar

Administration • 09.09.2019 - 01.06.2022

Document management and business correspondence;

Organization of supply of goods to the restaurant;

Organization of personnel work;

Management and control of the work schedule and vacations of employees;

Recruitment of staff for vacant positions in the restaurant;

Work with business documentation;

Briefing and training of staff, taking an exam on knowledge of the menu;

resolution of conflict situations, response to complaints and comments of guests;

Carrying out inventory, reporting (invoicing, implementation report, accrual of expenses, etc.).

#### **EDUCATION**

## **Bohdan Khmelnytsky National University of Cherkasy**

Master's • 09/2020 - 01/2022

Management of the educational institution

Primary school teacher

### **TOOLS**

SQL TestRail Swagger Zeplin Jira

#### **LANGUAGES**

English - Intermediate

Russian - Native

**Ukrainian** - Native